This mother and child have come to The SCOAN with a strange predicament.
The medical report states that the young child had swallowed a foreign object,
that is now stuck in his small throat.
The question is: What object did he swallow?
Shockingly, the X-ray of the one-year-old clearly shows a cross pendant securely lodged in his throat.
The presence of such a large foreign object in the throat of a one-year-old boy
must cause extreme discomfort and pain.
If the object is not removed, it could be fatal.
His mother has brought him to The SCOAN in desperate need of Divine intervention.
Let's hear what happened.
My name is Gift Stephen.
I come from Ebonyi State.
The baby I am carrying is my baby, Meshak Stephen - 1 year and five months.
Tell us the problem you have brought to The SCOAN today.
The problem that brought me here is that my baby swallowed a foreign object
which is stuck in his throat.
Ok. You mean your baby has a foreign object in his throat.
Yes.
He swallowed a cross pendant and since then, he cannot sleep at night.
We as parents, will also not be able to sleep; we will be awake until daybreak.
He vomits blood because of the pendant stuck in his throat.
When I took him to the chemist, they told me that he swallowed a cross pendant.
I reached for my cross necklace around my neck but realised it was not there.
The chain was still around my neck but the cross was missing - he had swallowed it.
The cross he swallowed was part of my necklace.
Where have you taken him to for solution?
I took him to the chemist first and then to many hospitals.
They told me that the only solution was an operation.
And now that you are here in The SCOAN today: What is your belief in Christ Jesus?
I believe Jesus will heal my son, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Healing Time
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministers prayer and deliverance to the people, in Jesus' name.
Among them is young Meshek Stephen and his mother who cries out to the man of God for help.
The lady is explaining that the baby she is holding swallowed a cross pendant as you can see in the X-ray.
So the cross pendant is now stuck in the throat of the baby.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Prayer & Deliverance In Jesus' Name
There is never a problem Jesus Christ cannot solve.
And with a touch from Heaven, he is free.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Gift. The man that is behind me is my husband.
The problem that brought me to this place was that of my son.
He swallowed a cross pendant.
What is the name of your son?
The name of my son is Meshack Stephen.
He swallowed a cross pendant when I was sleeping with him around 5:00 pm on Thursday.
The necklace clasp was open. He took it and swallowed it.
After he swallowed the cross pendant, I took him to the chemist.
The chemist said I should take him to the hospital, that it was serious.
I took him to the hospital and they took X-rays. The pendant could be seen.
I took him to another hospital and when we got there, the doctors said we should do another X-ray.
He said we should do an X-ray and come back.
We did the X-ray and could see the pendant; it had not moved at all.
We returned to the hospital.
They directed us to the place where they would operate on his neck to remove the pendant.
We were confused as to whether to perform the operation or not.
We took him out of the hospital because we were confused.
We brought him to The SCOAN and the man of God prayed for him.
When we got back home, my son vomited.
The next day, he started eating; before, he could only take custard or water.
Ok, let us take it one by one so that people will understand what you are saying.
So when your son swallowed the pendant, tell us what happened to your son.
When he swallowed the cross pendant, I was asleep.
When he started coughing and vomiting, I woke up.
My son vomited blood from his throat.
What were the things your son could not do then?
He could not sleep and he was always crying.
When he cried, he would point at his throat.
He was restless; he could not get himself.
What was he able to eat that time?
He could only drink tea, custard and water.
The mother further explained that when her son ingested this metallic cross object,
he could not eat then; the only thing her son could take were liquids.
The man of God prayed for him and after the prayer, we went back home.
That night, he vomited and after that, he slept.
When he woke up in the morning, I gave him tea.
He did not take the tea but kept pointing to the pot.
I gave him cooked food; he ate and did not vomit.
As it happened, he started eating everything he saw.
Because he was eating again, I took him back to the hospital to take another X-ray.
They could not find the pendant anymore.
Mrs Gift Stephen & Family
Prayer Line Testimony
The mother further explained to the glory of God that after the prayer of the man of God,
Prophet T.B.Joshua, that when they got home, her son started vomiting and stooling.
And when the vomiting stopped, they found out their son could eat normally.
They noticed that their son started eating anything he saw around.
He started eating the food they gave to him,
unlike before when he could only take tea or anything liquid
because of the metallic cross that was blocking the esophagus.
Even for him to swallow his own spit was a problem.
But after the prayer, their son was completely free.
Because their son had started eating, they took the boy to the same hospital that did the first X-ray
and they conducted another X-ray and found out that the object was no longer there.
That is what we are seeing on the screen right now.
Mrs Gift Stephen& Family
Prayer Line Testimony
As you can see on the screen of your television set, that is the X-ray that was taken
after the prayer of the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua that proves
that indeed, the object that was in the throat of their son is no longer there.
My name is Stephen Ogazie and the woman beside me is my wife and my son, Mesheck.
We both came from Ebonyi State, Nigeria.
As a matter of fact, I thank God for what God has done.
I came back from work and I found out that the child was vomiting blood.
So, I asked my wife what the matter was. She told me that she was looking for her cross pendant.
When they did the first X-ray and the report was brought to the doctor,
they saw an object, the cross pendant lodged in the child's throat.
The surgeon said that the only thing to do was to bring a certain amount of money,
N300,000 to N400,000, before he could start any work.
I began to recall some things that the Lord is doing in this great commission.
I knew that the case of this child was a solved case.
I knew fully well that if they had to operate on my child, they would not succeed
because that place is a delicate part of the body,
I knew that if this child underwent an operation, it would not succeed.
I began to have second thoughts, based on what the Lord is doing in this great commission.
I asked myself if it were not better that I run to God.
I had the opportunity on the 9th of September to come with my wife.
We had the opportunity to meet the man of God who laid hands on my child.
After that prayer, he pronounced liberty.
I was surprised.
As a matter of fact, we went back home that day and the vomiting increased.
I believe that the cross must have passed through that waste material.
We could not rest that night.
After that night, my child began to eat every food.
Initially, he was only taking liquids but he began to eat every type of food.
He began to point to particular food that we should bring for him.
When I saw that that was the case, I went back to the same surgeon.
I said, "Sir, there is something I want to verify". He said, "What is that?"
I said, "I want to run another test on this child".
He agreed, told me the price and put my child on the machine for the X-ray.
They brought the X-ray report to the doctor and he shouted.
He said, "Oga, what did you use to remove it?" I said, "I did not use anything, only prayer".
Mr Stephen Ogazie & Family
Prayer Line Testimony
I said, "I did not use anything but prayer!"
He asked, "What kind of prayer removed it because even the operation we had wanted to carry out
was not even enough as only a specialist could operate on that area in a child?"
I said, "We went to The SCOAN". The man shouted.
I said, "I came to The SCOAN for prayer and my child was privileged
to receive prayer from the man Of God which led to freedom".
He then redid the test from his neck to the sole of his feet and didn't find anything wrong.
He then asked, "Is this magic?"
I told him, "It is not magic but the work of Jesus!"
The man said I should give glory to God as no man could do such a thing.
He said that this was a case which only God could visit.
The man still questioned whether I used something to bring out the cross
as he did not see any sore or sign of pain.
I said, "There was nothing like that; it was just prayer.
The man of God laid hands on him and prayed and that was the end.
He then advised us with confidence that the case was settled".
The doctor himself was surprised.
He was surprised. He asked again, "Where did you visit?" I said, "The SCOAN".
Shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus.
What seems to be impossible with men is absolutely possible with God Almighty.
We have seen evidence that proves beyond reasonable doubt
that if not God, what do we think could have happened to this little boy?
But we give glory to God Almighty for this wonderful miracle that God has wrought in their life.
So tell us - what has been the condition of your son ever since then?
The condition of my child right from the day the man of God prayed for him -
he has not vomited since then.
The child has been free from all stress. He sleeps well; we hardly wake him.
He sleeps well, plays normally and can eat all kinds of food.
Because of this freedom, we determined to take him for a second X-ray, which we did.
This confirmed that the child now has a plain abdomen; the cross is no longer there.
When I met the doctor, I asked him to conduct another X-ray as practical evidence.
The doctor redid the X-ray and showed me the results on the screen.
He said, "There is no need to print it out as the case is settled and I should give glory to God".
Mr Stephen Ogazie & Family
Prayer Line Testimony
I just appreciate God. This is the first hospital we went where we were referred to another hospital.
Let's start from the top so that we can understand.
This is the first X-ray report which shows the child had an object in his lungs.
This is the second X-ray report which showed the cross was still there.
These reports you see here are referral letters to different hospitals.
This is the final X-ray report where the doctors confirmed there was no more foreign object.
They ran the test from the throat down to the abdomen and could not find the cross.
The man said we should give God thanks for settling this case as no man could do this but God.
So what we are seeing on the board is before and after.
Yes, before and after.
Shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus Christ.
Just down there we can also see an X-ray.
Can you just tell us more about the X-ray we seeing there?
Yes. This is the first X-ray.
This is the second X-ray where the doctors wanted to compare if the cross was in the same position.
Then the last one here...
Just take it one after the other so that people can understand.
We have three X-rays there.
The first one we are seeing there is the first X-ray that was conducted
and they found out that the boy had ingested a metallic cross object
that we are seeing right there on the esophagus of the boy before they came to The SCOAN.
And after the prayer of the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
they went to the same hospital, conducted another test, ran an X-ray -
and that's what we are seeing on the right hand side -
and found out that the boy is perfectly ok and the object is no longer there.
Mr Stephen Ogazie & Family
Prayer Line Testimony
The word of advice I'm giving to the world at large and people here inside The SCOAN is that
no matter the challenges or opposition of life you are facing, not matter the temptations or tests,
God is the last bus stop. Always seek Him and believe in Him.
It is not he who wrote your first letter who will determine your final result
but He who writes your final letter will determine your final result and that person is Jesus Christ.
Indeed, Jehovah has the final say.
Shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus Christ.
I want to advise mothers that when something like this happens to you, trust in God.
God can do anything.
Even if you carry your child in your hands, please be careful to watch over your child.
That was a word of advice from Madam Gift Stephen.
Now we want to encourage the family that now the Lord has set your son free,
as the Scripture says, "As for me and my family, we will serve the Lord",
we want you and your family to go and serve the Lord in Spirit and in truth
and train the child in the way of the Lord.
We pray that God Almighty will grant you and your family to grace to do so, in Jesus' name.
Once again shall we put our hands together for the miracle-working God.
TT Monica Asefa 25/07/18
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 31/07/2018 + Mel